let questionsArray = [
    {
        question: '“Is the dug deid?” means',
        answer1: 'A. Your trousers are too short',
        answer2: 'B. Something terrible has happened',
        answer3: 'C. Is the dog dead',
        answer4: 'D. The flag is at half mast',
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'If someone asked for some juice while at the shop they would expect',
        answer1: 'A. Alcohol',
        answer2: 'B. Fruit juice',
        answer3: 'C. Irn Bru',
        answer4: 'D. Gossip',
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following words does not mean girl',
        answer1: 'A. Quine',
        answer2: 'B. Hen',
        answer3: 'C. Lassie',
        answer4: 'D. Loon',
        correctAnswer: 4
    },
    {
        question: '“Tea-time” is usually around',
        answer1: 'A. 8am to 10am',
        answer2: 'B. 11am to 1pm',
        answer3: 'C. 3pm to 5pm',
        answer4: 'D. 6pm to 8pm',
        correctAnswer: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'If you were “away to do some messages”, you would be',
        answer1: 'A. Doing some food shopping',
        answer2: 'B. Writing postcards',
        answer3: 'C. Checking your email',
        answer4: 'D. Going on a date',
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following is not a food?',
        answer1: 'A. Neeps',
        answer2: 'B. Tatties',
        answer3: 'C. Drams',
        answer4: 'D. Stovies',
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'The word “pelters” refers to',
        answer1: 'A. Insults',
        answer2: 'B. Inclement Weather',
        answer3: 'C. Shoes',
        answer4: 'D. Nails',
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'The use of the word “poke” means',
        answer1: 'A. Hawaiian food',
        answer2: 'B. To prod someone',
        answer3: 'C. A container of chips',
        answer4: 'D. To get sick',
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'If someone said you looked “peely-wally” they would mean',
        answer1: 'A. Dapper',
        answer2: 'B. Sickly',
        answer3: 'C. Unkempt',
        answer4: 'D. In need of moisturiser',
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following words is not used to describe something unpleasant',
        answer1: 'A. Manky',
        answer2: 'B. Mingin\'',
        answer3: 'C. Boggin\'',
        answer4: 'D. Wain',
        correctAnswer: 4
    },
    {
        question: '“Ken-fit-ah-min” is a phrase that means',
        answer1: 'A. A medication',
        answer2: 'B. Ken is fit and mean',
        answer3: 'C. Do you understand',
        answer4: 'D. These trews are a snug fit',
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: '“Tatties o\’wer the side” is a phrase that means',
        answer1: 'A. Something has gone terribly wrong',
        answer2: 'B. Man overboard',
        answer3: 'C. A side of potatoes',
        answer4: 'D. You\’ve eaten too much',
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following names is not also a slang word',
        answer1: 'A. Barry',
        answer2: 'B. Nick',
        answer3: 'C. Bonnie',
        answer4: 'D. Andrew',
        correctAnswer: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'The term “dinghy” means',
        answer1: 'A. Something has been damaged',
        answer2: 'B. An intention to ignore something',
        answer3: 'C. A bell rang',
        answer4: 'D. A boat',
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following does not mean drunk',
        answer1: 'A. Steamin\’',
        answer2: 'B. Reakin\’',
        answer3: 'C. Greetin\’',
        answer4: 'D. Oot ma nut',
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'If someone asked you “far div ya bide” they would be asking you',
        answer1: 'A. Where do you live',
        answer2: 'B. How far did you cycle',
        answer3: 'C. Where do you work',
        answer4: 'D. Have you been on a holiday',
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'The term “dinna fash yersel” means',
        answer1: 'A. Don\’t go to too much trouble',
        answer2: 'B. How was dinner',
        answer3: 'C. Watch yourself',
        answer4: 'D. Don\’t make yourself sick',
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: '“An empty” on a night out would be in reference to',
        answer1: 'A. Funds',
        answer2: 'B. A house party',
        answer3: 'C. Dancefloor',
        answer4: 'D. Glass',
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following words is used to describe feeling queasy',
        answer1: 'A. Belter',
        answer2: 'B. Stoater',
        answer3: 'C. Braw',
        answer4: 'D. Boak',
        correctAnswer: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'If asked to give someone a “bosie”, you would give them a',
        answer1: 'A. Kiss',
        answer2: 'B. Compliment',
        answer3: 'C. Cuddle',
        answer4: 'D. Telling off',
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
];